Guide to the Public Administration Reports and Studies (Assorted), 1910-1992 AIS.1996.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Reports on Pittsburgh (city), 1910-1985; IV.
  - Department of Public Safety: Bureau of Fire, 1939-1983; 25
    - Annual Report, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Laws and Regulations, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Department of Public Safety: Bureau of Police, 1937-1973; 26
    - Annual Report, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Annual Report, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Annual Report, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Annual Report, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Annual Report, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Annual Report, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Annual Report, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Service Brunch Yearly Report, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Statistical Report, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Statistical Report, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Statistical Report, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Statistical Report, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - A Survey of the Bureau of Police, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Department of Public Safety: Bureau of Traffic Planning/Division of Traffic Information, 1947-1965; 27
    - Annual Report, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Traffic Accident Summary, 1947-1965 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Traffic Accident Summary, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Traffic Accident Summary, nine months, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Pittsburgh Area Transportation Study, 1959-1960; 28
    - Coding Manual, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Digest Report, Undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Estimating the Daily Vehicle Miles of Travel in the Chicago and Pittsburgh Metropolitan Areas, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Interim Technical Report Number II, Accuracy Checks, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Interim Technical Report Number III, Home Interview Summary Data, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Measurement of Highway Capacity, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Publications, Undated (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Department of Public Health, 1942-1948; 29
    - Annual Report, 1942 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Annual Report, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Personnel Policies Manual, Undated (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Report on Railroad Smoke Condition, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Survey Report, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 45)
- Reports on the Turtle Creek Valley (borough and region), 1955-1973; V.
  - Turtle Creek Valley Labor Market Study, Volume I, 1971 (Box 8)
  - Manual to Accompany Turtle Creek Valley Labor Market Study, 1971
  - Turtle Creek Valley Labor Market Study, Volume II, 1971
  - Turtle Creek Valley Model Cities Program, Education Survey Volume II, 1971
  - Turtle Creek Valley Model Cities Program, Education Survey Volume I, 1971
  - Turtle Creek Valley Model Cities Program, Resident Employment and Training Plan, 1971
  - Turtle Creek Valley Model Cities, Labor Force Phase II Study, Final Report, 1972
  - Fiscal Studies and Projections 1964 through 1974 for Each of Eleven Municipalities Within the Turtle Creek Valley Model Neighborhood, Undated
  - Turtle Creek Valley Model Cities, Labor Force Phase II Study, Final Report, 1972
  - Turtle Creek Valley Model Cities, Labor Force Phase II Study, Procedures Manual, 1972
  - Turtle Creek Valley Model Cities, Labor Force Phase II Study, 1972
  - Turtle Creek Valley Model Cities, Operating Agency Contract Requirements Manual, 1972
  - Turtle Creek Model Neighborhood Consultants Report on Physical Environment, 1970
  - Comprehensive Park and Recreation Plan for Turtle Creek Valley Model Cities, 1973
  - Comprehensive Sewer and Water Facility Study of the Turtle Creek Valley Model Neighborhood, 1972
  - Intergovernmental Relations and Public Works Management, 1972
  - Preliminary Program Documentation Manual for the Turtle Creek Valley Improvement Program (TCVIP), 1972 (Box 7)
  - Review of Reports Upon Turtle Creek Basin, Turtle Creek, Pennsylvania, 1957
  - Turtle Creek, PA. Flood Control, 1958
  - A Long-Range Plan of Improvement for Lower Turtle Creek Valley (Oversize), 1955 (Box 9)
- Reports on Municipal Governments in Pennsylvania, 1947-83; VI.
  - Aliquippa, Statistical Abstract of Aliquippa, Pennsylvania, 1952 (Box 24)
  - Aliquippa, A Comprehensive Community Development Plan, 1977
  - Allentown, New Water Supply Sources for the Allentown-Lehigh County Area: An Issue Paper for the Sewer and Water Plan Update, 1979
  - Allentown, Additional Sewage Treatment Capacity for the Allentown-Lehigh County Area: An Issue Paper for the Sewer and Water Plan Update, 1979
  - Allentown, City of Allentown Master Sewer Plan, 1977
  - Altoona, Recreation Master Plan Report 11, 1969
  - Altoona, Altoona Area Transportation Study, Volume I Data Collection and Inventories, 1966
  - Altoona, Altoona Area Transportation Study, Volume II Analysis and Forecasts, 1967
  - Altoona, Natural Conditions Master Plan Report III, 1969
  - Ambridge, Statistical Abstract of Ambridge Pennsylvania, 1952
  - Armstrong County, Rural Sewer Improvement Plan, 1980
  - Armstrong County, County Data Book, 1981
  - Armstrong County, Rural Water Improvement Plan, 1978
  - Armstrong County, Neighborhood Recreation Facilities Plan (Oversize), 1978 (Box 9)
  - Aspinwall, Aspinwall Borough Comprehensive Plan, 1964 (Box 24)
  - Athens, An Industrial Site Feasibility Study, Economic Development Administration, 1968
  - Baldwin, Urban Renewal Recommendations for the Borough of Baldwin, Undated
  - Baldwin, Comprehensive Plan Part I, 1967
  - Baldwin, Comprehensive Plan Parts II/III, 1968
  - Beaver County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Beaver County, Flood Plain Information: Ohio and Beaver Rivers, Beaver County, 1973
  - Beaver Falls, Statistical Abstract of Beaver Falls, Pennsylvania, 1952
  - Beaver Falls, City of Beaver Falls Comprehensive Plan, 1969
  - Bedford County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Bentleyville, General Development Plan Guide for Action, Undated
  - Berks County, Fire Protection Study, 1977
  - Berks County, Technical Report: Reading Area Transportation Study, 1969
  - Berks County, Technical Report: Reading Area Transportation Study, 1969
  - Berks County, Police Protection Study, 1977
  - Berks County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Berks County, Land Use Coding Manual for Urbanized Land Area use Surveys and Rural Area Land use Surveys, 1976
  - Berks County, Highway Planning and Implementation in Berks County Status Report, 1969
  - Berks County, Status Report: Mass Transportation and Highway Planning and Implementation, 1970
  - Berks County, Technical Report: Reading Area Transportation Study: Evaluation of Land-Use and Socio-Economic Impacts, 1970
  - Bethel Park, A Long Range Development Plan, 1963
  - Bethlehem, East Bethlehem Township Comprehensive Plan Summary, 1967
  - Bethlehem, East Bethlehem Township Planning Administration and Financing, 1967
  - Blair County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Blair County, AATS Bikeway Plan Phasing Schedule, 1978
  - Blair County, Recreation Facilities Inventory, 1977
  - Blair County, Recreation Experience Standards, 1977
  - Blair County, Recreation Interest Survey, 1976
  - Bloomsburg, Comprehensive Storm Water Plan, 1975
  - Boswell, Comprehensive Plan Technical Report, c1960 (Box 25)
  - Braddock, Statistical Abstract of Braddock, Pennsylvania, 1953
  - Braddock, Preliminary Draft of the Provisions for the Special Planned Urban Revitalization District, 1977
  - Braddock, Addenda to the Preliminary Draft of the Provisions for the Special Planned Urban Revitalization District, 1977
  - Bradford County, Existing and Future Thoroughfare Plans of the Member Counties of the Northern Tier Regional Planning and Development Regional Planning Commission for the Pennsylvania Counties of Bradford, Sullivan, Susquehanna, Tioga, and Wyoming, 1979
  - Bradford County, Bradford Pennsylvania, Bureau of Business Research, 1953
  - Bradford County, Recreation and Open Space Plan, 1971
  - Bradfordwoods, Planning Administration and Financing for Bradfordwoods Borough, 1962
  - Brady, Implementation Report: Proposed Zoning Ordinance, Proposed Mobile Home Ordinance, and Proposed Subdivision Regulations, 1970
  - Brownsville, Research and Survey Report, 1958
  - Bridgeville, Guide for Action, Planning Procedures and Programs, Undated
  - Bucks County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Bucks County, A Regional Park System, Boards of County Commissioners of Bucks, Chester, Delaware, and Montgomery Counties and the Mayor of the City of Philadelphia, 1956
  - Bucks County, The Economic Profile 1960-1968, 1971
  - Bucks County, An Expressway System for the Southeastern Pennsylvania Region, Chairmen of Bucks, Chester, Delaware, and Montgomery County Planning Commissions and the Philadelphia City Planning Commission, 1955
  - Butler County, Park, Recreation, and Open Space Plan Part I, 1971
  - Butler County, Park, Recreation, and Open Space Plan Part II (Oversize), 1972 (Box 9)
  - Butler County, County Data Book, 1982 (Box 25)
  - Butler County, A Plan for the Central Areas of Butler, Pennsylvania, Planning and Zoning Commission, Undated
  - Butler County, Land Use Study: Physical Features Study, 1965
  - Butler County, The Old Stone House, Undated
  - Burgettstown, Guide for Action, 1970
  - Burgettstown, Neighborhood Analysis and Plans, 1969
  - Cambria County, Cambria/Somerset Disaster Recovery Plan, 1979
  - Cambria County, Inventory of Historical Sites, 1976
  - Cambria County, Solid Waste Management Study Digest Report, 1971
  - Cambria County, Analysis of Historic Preservation, 1976
  - Cambria County, Monitoring Programs for Erosion and Sediment Control and Storm Drainage, 1976
  - Cambria County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Cambria County, Industrial Development Analysis, 1971
  - Cambria County, Economic Base, 1969
  - Cambria County, Recreation Plan Update: Facility and Program Inventory, 1977
  - Cambria County, Highway and Transportation Plan, 1969
  - Cambria County, Open Space and Recreation Study, 1969
  - Cambria County, Human Services Study, 1976
  - Cambria County, Rural Mass Transit Study, 1976
  - Cambria County, Mass Transit, 1975
  - Cambria County, Water Resources Study, 1969
  - Cambria County, Flood Plain Management Plan, 1977
  - Cambria County, Flood Plain Management Plan, 1978
  - Cameron County, County Data Book, 1982 (Box 26)
  - Carbon County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Carbon County, Economic Indicators of Northeastern Pennsylvania 1957-1975, 1976
  - Carbondale, Statistical Abstract of Carbondale, Pennsylvania, 1957
  - Carlisle, Statistical Abstract of Carlisle, Pennsylvania, 1954
  - Centre County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Centre County, Water and Sewer Study: Update and Projections, 1976
  - Centre County, Rural Mass Transit Study, 1975
  - Centre County, Land Use/ Open Space Plan Evaluation and Policies, 1976
  - Centreville, Planning Administration and Financing, 1967
  - Centreville, Comprehensive Plan Survey, 1971
  - Chalfant, Capital Improvements Program, c1972
  - Chartiers Valley, Planning Report: Stage One, Chartiers Valley Industrial Study Area, 1960
  - Chartiers Valley, Basic Conditions Report: Stage One, Chartiers Valley Industrial Study Area, 1960
  - Chartiers Valley, Preliminary Broadhead Fording Redevelopment Area Plan No. 13, 1961
  - Chartiers Valley, Floods in the Chartiers Valley, 1957
  - Chartiers Valley, Chartiers Creek Valley, Letter from the Secretary of the Army, 1964
  - Chester County, The Brandywine Plan for the Upper East Branch of Brandywine Creek (Oversize), 1968 (Box 38)
  - Churchill, Capital Improvements Program for Churchill Borough, c1972 (Box 26)
  - Clarion County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Clairton, Proposal for a Community Renewal Program, 1966
  - Clairton, Clairton Pennsylvania, Bureau of Business Research, 1953
  - Clairton, General Plan, 1963
  - Clearfield County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Clearfield County, Clearfield Pennsylvania, Bureau of Business Research, 1954
  - Clinton, Implementation Report: Proposed Zoning Ordinance, Proposed Mobile Home Ordinance, Proposed Subdivision Regulations and Illustrative Capital Improvements Program, 1970
  - Clinton, The Impact of Interchange Development on the Economy of Clinton County, 1966
  - Clinton County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Collier, A Program for Collier, 1961
  - Collier, Progress Report: Feasibility Study, 1964
  - Columbia County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Columbia County, Economic Base Study, 1967
  - Connellsville, Housing, Land Use and Zoning Report, 1959
  - Connellsville, Research and Survey Report, 1958
  - Connellsville, An Administrative Study, 1963
  - Crafton, Renewal of the Core Area, Undated
  - Crawford County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Cross Creek, Planning Administration and Financing, 1965
  - Cumberland County, Storm Water Management Plan Phase II, 1977
  - Cumberland County, A Guide for Flood Damage Prevention Ordinance, 1976
  - Cumberland County, A Guide for Building Permit Ordinance Short Form and Long Form, 1976
  - Cumberland County, A Guide for a Sign Ordinance, 1976
  - Cumberland County, Conservation and Open Space Plan, 1975
  - Dauphin County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Deemston, Comprehensive Plan Summary, 1967
  - Deemston, Planning Administration and Financing, 1967
  - Delaware County, Making Commercial Strips Work: An Urban Design Study, 1976
  - Delaware County, Air Pollution Emissions Summary, 1968
  - Delaware County, Meteorology and Air Pollution Summary, 1968
  - Delaware County, Governmental Aspects Summary, 1968
  - Derry, Derry Township Comprehensive Plan, 1970 (Box 27)
  - Derry, Derry Borough Comprehensive Plan, 1970
  - Donora, Industrial Site Study Final Report, 1967
  - Doylestown, Neighborhood Analysis, 1966
  - Doylestown, Design Resources for Doylestown, 1969
  - Duquesne, Statistical Abstract of Duquesne, Pennsylvania, 1953
  - Duquesne, Comprehensive Development Plan, 1970
  - Easton, A Plan for Downtown Easton 1964-1984, Undated
  - Edgemont, Plan Implementation Phase Four, Delaware County Planning Committee, Undated
  - Elk County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Erie, Comprehensive Metropolitan Erie Community Analysis Planning Area Profiles, 1967
  - Erie, Downtown Erie Renewal, Undated
  - Erie, Overall Program Design for Erie City and Erie County 1975-1978, Erie Metropolitan Planning Commission
  - Erie, The Economical, Environmental (Social), Governmental, and Historical Aspects of Erie, Pennsylvania, 1972
  - Erie, Your Downtown, 1969
  - Erie, Solid Waste Collection, 1974
  - Erie, New Erie, Redevelopment Authority of the City of Erie, Pennsylvania, c1970
  - Erie, Proposed Erie City-County Water Service, 1978
  - Erie, City-wide Neighborhood Analysis, 1975
  - Erie, Statistical Abstract of Erie, Pennsylvania, 1954
  - Erie County, Land Use Plan, 1971
  - Erie County, Erie County Highways and Mass Transit Plan, 1970
  - Erie County, Public Utilities Study, 1970
  - Erie County, Parks and Open Space Plan, 1970
  - Erie County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Erie County, Land Use: An Interim Report, 1970
  - Erie County Water Supply and Distribution Plan, Part II: The Non-Metropolitan Area, Undated
  - Etna, Comprehensive Plan, 1981
  - Fallowfield, General Development Plan, Undated
  - Fayette County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Findlay, Background for Planning, 1963
  - Forest County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Forest Hills, Housing Improvement Program for Forest Hills Borough, Undated
  - Fox Chapel, A Comprehensive Development Plan, 1963
  - Franklin, Comprehensive Plan, 1970
  - Franklin County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Greene County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Greencastle, Economic and Population Analysis, 1964
  - Greensburg, General Nature and History of Development, 1958 (Box 28)
  - Greensburg, Central Business District Call for Action, 1965
  - Greensburg, Central Business District Technical Report, 1965
  - Greensburg, Statistical Abstract of Greensburg, Pennsylvania, 1953
  - Greensburg, Urban Renewal, Undated
  - Greensburg, Background Report for the Greater Greensburg General Plan, 1967
  - Green Tree, A Long Range Development Plan, 1964
  - Harrisburg, The Future of Downtown Harrisburg: Market Analysis and Projections, 1963
  - Harrisburg, Interim Report on Space Inventory and Related Information for Capitol Complex and Adjacent Areas, c1970
  - Homewood-Brushton, Homewood-Brushton Community Center: A Feasibility Study, 1967
  - Homewood-Brushton, A Social Plan for Homewood-Brushton, 1983
  - Hopewell, Comprehensive Plan Summary, 1965
  - Huntingdon, East Huntingdon Township Guide for Action, Undated
  - Huntingdon, Master Plan for North Huntingdon, 1958
  - Huntingdon County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Huntingdon County, Comprehensive Plan, 1971
  - Huntingdon County, Conservation Plan, 1978
  - Independence, Comprehensive Plan Summary, 1965
  - Indiana, A Parks, Recreation, and Open Space Study, 1970
  - Jeanette, Statistical Abstract of Jeanette, Pennsylvania, 1953
  - Jeanette, A Study of Jeanette Fire Department, 1957
  - Jefferson, Urban Renewal Recommendations, c1968
  - Jefferson, Planning, Administration, and Financing, 1965
  - Jefferson, Comprehensive Plan Summary, 1965
  - Jefferson, A Plan for Future Growth: Comprehensive Plan and Policies, 1968
  - Jefferson County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Jenkintown, New Communities: Annotated Bibliography, 1971
  - Johnstown, The Environmental Plan 1976-1977
  - Johnstown, Johnstown Area Transportation Study: Data Collection Inventories, 1969
  - Johnstown, Cooperative Recreation Program, 1975
  - Johnstown, Vertical Land Use Analysis, 1976
  - Johnstown, Multiple Use of Public Buildings, 1975 (Box 29)
  - Johnstown, Prospect Neighborhood Renewal Plan, 1973
  - Johnstown, Statistical Abstract of Johnstown, Pennsylvania, 1953
  - Juniata County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Lackawanna County, Regional and Open Space Plan, 1971
  - Lackawanna County, Solid Waste Plan, 1976
  - Lackawanna County, New Community for Lackawanna County, 1975
  - Lackawanna County, Comprehensive Analysis and Action Alternatives for Northeastern Pennsylvania, 1970
  - Lancaster County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Lancaster County, Sample Floodplain District Zoning Ordinance Provisions, 1977
  - Lancaster County, The Queen Street Project and Lancaster's Urban Renewal Program, 1963
  - Latrobe, Population-Economic Studies, Latrobe/Unity Regional Plan, 1966
  - Latrobe, Development Plan and Proposals, 1966
  - Lawrence County, Industrial Development Plan, 1975
  - Lawrence County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Lawrence County, Recreation Study, 1980
  - Lawrence County, Economic Survey, 1963
  - Lawrence County, Interchange Study, 1967
  - Lawrence County, Traffic and Circulation, 1963
  - Lawrenceville, Land Use Study, 1976
  - Lebanon County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Lehigh County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Lehigh Valley, Employment Outlook, 1977-1978
  - Ligonier, A Master Plan, 1962
  - Lehigh County, Regional Recreation and Open Space Plan, 1980
  - Lehigh County, Regional Recreation and Open Space Plan, 1977
  - Lehigh County, Water Supply and Sewage Facilities Plan, 1979
  - Lehigh County, South Mountain (Oversize), 1977 (Box 38)
  - Lehigh County, Water Supply and Sewage Facilities Plan Supplement, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Lehigh County, Water Conservation: Governmental Policies, A Survey of Local Systems, and Benefits to Consumers and Suppliers, 1980
  - Lehigh County, Regional Storm Drainage Plan, 1980
  - Luzerne County, The Luzerne Township Plan, Undated
  - Luzerne County, Regional Water System: Back Mountain Area, 1962
  - Luzerne County, Housing Report, 1960
  - Luzerne County, Climate, Topography, and Population, 1962
  - Lycoming County, Regional Energy Policies Plan, 1979 (Box 30)
  - Lycoming County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Lycoming County, Comprehensive Water and Sewer Plan, 1969
  - Lycoming County, Transportation Study, 1969
  - McDonald, Guide for Action: Planning, Procedures, and Program, Undated
  - McKean County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Meyersdale, Statistical Abstract of Meyersdale, Pennsylvania, 1954
  - McKeesport, Report on Disaster Urban Renewal Project PA. R-442, Analysis of Physical Development Potential- Existing and Future, 1977
  - McKeesport, Profile of Minimum Highway Needs for the Greater McKeesport Area, Undated
  - McKeesport, A Master Plan (Oversize), Undated (Box 38)
  - McKeesport, Community Renewal Plan, 1968 (Box 30)
  - McKeesport, An Economic Analysis, 1960
  - McKeesport, Community Renewal Plan, 1968
  - McKeesport, Land Use Plan for the McKeesport Disaster Area, Appendix, 1978
  - McKeesport, Community Renewal Program, 1968
  - McKees Rocks, A Plan for Transition, Undated
  - Meadville, Comprehensive General Plan, 1958
  - Mercer County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Mifflin County, Commercial and Industrial Study, 1977
  - Mifflin County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Mifflin County, Update of the County-Wide Water and Sewer Plan, 1979
  - Millvale, Flood Insurance Study, 1979
  - Monessen, Neighborhood Analysis, 1965
  - Monessen, Study of Monessen Fire Department, 1957
  - Monessen, Statistical Abstract of Monessen, Pennsylvania, 1953
  - Monroe County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Monroeville, Selected Attitudes Toward Highway Change, 1964
  - Monroeville, Flood Insurance Study, 1979
  - Monroeville, Master Land Acquisition for Recreation Areas (Oversize), 1961 (Box 38)
  - Montgomery, General Plan Report, 1970 (Box 30)
  - Montgomery, Implementation Report, 1970
  - Montgomery County, Land Use Plan Survey, 1969
  - Montgomery County, Zoning Boards of Adjustment, 1964
  - Montgomery County, Commuter Rail Extension Plan, 1978 (Box 31)
  - Montgomery County, Resource Protection Plan, 1976
  - Montour County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Mount Lebanon, A Central Core Study, 1962
  - Mount Lebanon, Long Range Developmental Program, Mount Lebanon School District, 1968
  - Mount Lebanon, Annual Report, Mount Lebanon Department of Police, 1979
  - Mount Lebanon, Long Range Comprehensive Plan Development Policies, 1969
  - Mount Pleasant, Planning, Administration, and Financing, 1965
  - Monongahela Valley, A Guide for Leisure, Living, and Recreation, 1968
  - Monongahela Valley, Educational Program Plan of Mon Valley Area Vocational-Technical School, 1969
  - Monongahela Valley, Air Pollution Study, 1969
  - Monongahela Valley, An Analysis of Short-Range Needs for Mass Transportation Within the Mid-Monongahela Valley, 1977
  - Monongahela Valley, Study of the Mon Valley Recreation and Character Building Services for the Mon Valley United Fund, 1965
  - Monongahela Valley, Recreation: A Move Toward Implementation in the Mon Valley, 1968
  - New Alexandria, Comprehensive Plan, 1970
  - New Castle, New Castle Bypass, 1961
  - New Castle, Mass Transportation in a Small City, The New Castle Area Transit Authority, 1968
  - New Castle, Statistical Abstract of New Castle, Pennsylvania, 1953
  - New Castle, Neighborhood Analysis, 1966
  - New Kensington, Core Area Renewal Study, 1963
  - New Wilmington, Background Report #1: Land Use Study and Community Facilities, 1962
  - New Wilmington, Background Report #2: Physical Characteristics and Population, 1962
  - New Wilmington, Background Report #3: Traffic & Circulation and Economic Base, 1962
  - New Wilmington, A Comprehensive Plan, 1963
  - Norristown, Parking Survey, 1951
  - Norristown, Statistical Abstract of Norristown, Pennsylvania, 1958
  - North Huntingdon, Master Plan Report, Item 6: Utilities, 1958
  - North Huntingdon, Master Plan Reports, Item 7: Schools, 1958
  - North Huntingdon, Master Plan Reports, Item 8: Recreation, 1958
  - Northampton County, County Data Report, 1982
  - Northumberland County, Public Facilities, 1980
  - Oakdale, Guide for Action: Planning, Procedures, and Programs, Undated
  - Oakmont, Part of a Master Plan Report, Item 13- Public Buildings, 1958
  - Oakmont, Part of a Master Plan Report, Item 12- Urban Renewal, 1958